[Music]
I'm going to give it to you straight you
need Blitz it and it's not just because
my team and I built it it's because we
built it for people like us and we're
like you super busy people who need to
stay on track in a world full of
distractions and digital clutter and
that's why we built Blitz it Blitz it
transforms your personal productivity by
bringing all of your scattered tasks
into one beautiful actionable daily list
that's always Within Reach complete with
a lifetimer that keeps you on track
minute by minute and is packed with so
many cool features that helps you
achieve unwavering Flow State so you can
win your day every day let me show you
how it works organize your task into
lists add time estimates schedule them
and prioritize your day effortlessly
when you're ready to dive in hit that
Blitz button to drop into Flow State
start your day with a live timer on your
first task while everything else stays
neatly organized out of the way yet
always in reach if you need to Double
Down switch to focus mode a tiny
floating timer keeps you on track
without distractions as you work you can
quickly add subtasks notes links keeping
important details at your fingertips and
if your attention drifts Blitz it nudges
you with a flashy
ding reminding you to stay focused and
when you complete a task smash that done
button to celebrate your progress and
keep the momentum going again and again
and again and maybe after a few tasks
take a break you deserve it it's really
that simple and that's just the
beginning Blitz it is packed with
powerful features to supercharge your
workflow seamlessly sync with notion and
Google Calendar with more Integrations
on the horizon to make Blitz it truly
yours you can personalize your
experience choose from different timer
tracking modes including a pomodora
timer or switch themes and much more use
shortcuts for quick actions while
staying in flow we've also built-in
reports to track your time spent and get
valuable insights on your productivity
and look we're building more than just a
tool we're cultivating a community of
productive passionate people that are
motivated to master their day and in
fact our entire Community is helping us
plan an ambitious road map for the
future including a mobile app which is
coming soon AI assistance list sharing
and so much more so if you want to
remove distractions focus on what
matters and get things done all in Flow
State try Blitz it for free today also
for a limited time of running a Early
Access lifetime deal and currently the
price is slashed by 30% very soon we'll
be switching this to an annual plan so
don't miss out